I want you to create a simple tap window that user can add an API locally, and replace my API.
So it won't be arts copied and make it in the main page of an extension.
Please provide a link directly to the place where we can obtain a create API.
Because we use alpha vintage, how is this, double vintage.
And this is the direct URL.
I'll just copy it over.
And this is where we can just set it up, and then our presenter, and then need to add additional
feature.
So you can see it's adding a script.
Now it's replacing.
So API will not be hard coded in repository.
OK, we see the others if you add to options file.
So I will go to the extension tab, go to manage, our refresh, my stock, and I will just
open it up now.
And here we will have our trading, here are settings, and this is the API key that we have
it here.
That's great.
So we put it in the settings, it will automatically go, here are profiles.
So this one we can directly apply it here.
So it will not be hard coded, because now if I go to my place and try to look with my
extension, here are options, API key has to use the API key that we add.
Obviously we can search here, build the API service, and then it's just a variable, it's
not hard coded number, because when I tap an API and search on my repository, it will not
find anything.
Still, if we go to now extension, and go directly here, we can directly separate.
So don't like the settings, so this is the way.
But we can add, if we don't have an API, we can also add in, we see it's 3/2, 24 requests,
and it can save us.
So it's pretty great.
All right, so this is it.
In the next video we create a longevity extension.
I will more be wise on to the list, not like API.
This is another version, and I think it's great when you can test it out and create your
own simulation, in the next video is how we can extend some of the halves and add them
to a Chrome extension store.